sewplicity.com 2018-03-27

# Privacy Policy - Sewplicity

This privacy policy sets out how Sewplicity®, LLC uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website. Sewplicity®,LLC is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Sewplicity®,LLC may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1/1/2009. ** **

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you

  * Register on our site
  * Fill out the Reservation Form
  * Place and order
  * Respond to a survey
  * Fill out a form

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your:

  * Name
  * Email Address
  * Mailing Address
  * Phone Number

## What we use your information for?

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping
  * To personalize your experience
  * To improve our products and services
  * To improbe customer service
  * We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email or mail.
  * To process transactions
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

## How we use cookies

****A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. ** **

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

****We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.  This does not include trusted third parties who assist in operating our website, conducting our business, or service you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies or protect ours from others’ rights, property or safety.  However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Links to other websites

****Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. ** **

## Copyright & Usage

### Any redistribution or reproduction of part or all of the contents in any form is prohibited other than the following:

  * you may print or download content for your personal and non-commercial use only.
  * you may link to a document or image that is hosted on our website, but please include an attribution to Sewplicity with the link.
  * you may share the content in social media as long as it links back to the original post.

You may not, distribute or commercially exploit the content. For example, you may not:

  * copy any of our content pages.
  * reproduce our tutorials and post them on your site.

## Photo Submissions Terms and Conditions

By posting or submitting your photo to Sewplicity, LLC through email, snail mail or electronic form, you warrant and represent that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to your submission including, but not limited to, all the rights necessary for you to provide, post, upload, input or submit the photo. You warrant and represent that (a) you are the copyright owner of the photo submitted, or the copyright owner of such photo has granted you permission to use the photo; and (b) that you are the depicted child’s parent/legal guardian. You understand that your photo, if approved, may be used in Sewplicity’s brand advertisements without compensation to your child or yourself and you consent to such use.

By submitting a photo to Sewplicity, LLC you agree that the Sewplicity may use, edit, alter or distribute the photo for marketing, advertising, or any promotional purposes.  You consent to indemnify Sewplicity, LLC against any claim, demand, action, suit or other proceedings agains Sewplicity arising out of the use of the photograph and related to any false or inaccurate statement.
